(Leonard:)Did you get the part?
(Penny:)No, they said I was too perky.
Wanna talk about not getting
love from a parent?
(Leonard:)You know what I used to do when I was
little to have sensation of human contact?
(Penny:)Yeah, you grabbed your penis
and wouldn't let go.
(Penny:)Your mother told me.
[LEONARD SCOFFS]
(Leonard:)Of course she did.
That's not what I was gonna say.
Uh... Uh, when I was 10-years old,
I built a hugging machine.
- A hugging machine?
- Yeah.
I got a mannequin, stuffed it
with an electric blanket so it'd be warm...
...and I built two radio-controlled arms
that would hug me and pat my back.
(Penny:)Oh, that is so sad.
(Leonard:)- Know what the saddest part was?
- What?
(Leonard:)My father used to borrow it.
(Beverley:)Your scan data
will be very helpful to my research.
(Beverley:)You have a remarkable brain.